[SPEAKER_01]: I go over his career here and I'm sure you'll hear some very interesting stories.
[SPEAKER_01]: What I'd like to have you do, Mr. Kalk, is to first, at the beginning, tell me how you broke into baseball, who scouted you, and maybe where you were playing before you became a professional, the early days, so you can depict the whole picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Mr. Murdock, I was born in a little town
[SPEAKER_02]: in St. Charles County, Missouri, October 16, 1900.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, my dad moved from there into St. Louis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's where I was going to grade school there, and we had a ball club, and I could throw pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as I got bigger, I could throw harder, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we played a team that was managed by Ralph Works, the old Detroit pitcher, and I pitched the ball game against him in the
[SPEAKER_02]: semi-pro league down there and I pitched a no-hitter against you.
[SPEAKER_02]: In St. Louis?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's in St. Louis.
[SPEAKER_01]: How old were you then?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seventeen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: A no-hitter, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: So then he decided to come back several years after that when I got to pitch in the Munity now in St. Louis and had a pretty good record.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a good fastball but I was wild and that kept the hitter a little bit loose up the plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway,
[SPEAKER_02]: This fellow, Ralph Wilkes, remembered me, so he came out to my house one day and he asked my dad where I was.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was 19 then.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went up to him to show where he was, and he come and got me out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he wanted to know if I wanted to play professional ball, and I said, yes, I would.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went to Madison, South Dakota.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my first year out in 1900.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, he was the Detroit.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a Detroit scout, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you signed with a Detroit... No, I signed with Madison because I was underage and my father had to okay my contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I had signed a contract with the Pat Monahan and the St. Louis Browns.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I didn't know the difference, so I signed two contracts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the Browns contract was tore up and I went to Madison.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who tore it up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who tore the Browns contract up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pat Monahan did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, there was another one he couldn't accept because I had... You signed with the St. Louis Counter after the other one?
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't know about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I signed with Madison first, see, and then I signed with him.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I went up there and I had a pretty good career.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me a little bit about your family.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd your father do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my father was a farmer.
[SPEAKER_02]: They worked on a farm down in Walden Springs for all of Wally's folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then he moved to St. Louis where he was a farmer for the Fort Lamberts.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did he think of your playing ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he thought it was alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of tickled him a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, he got me started with baseball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he play ball himself?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, he didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was he pretty proud of you playing ball?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he get to see you play much?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about your mother?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did she like it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mother, well, she didn't know anything about baseball.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was with the Anchor this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were playing at St. Louis and had
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, Nick Cullip's single is spoiled playing against the Browns.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, well, I've played the ball game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They went out there and saw it, mother and father and my sister.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I hit a double and I slid in the second base.
[SPEAKER_02]: The next fellow was single and I slid in the home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the paper said that Nick Cullip started at the Yankees beat the Browns 43 and my mother still remembered me sliding in the second and sliding in the home.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I asked her after the ball game was over and my dad would walk around us moving carts on pipes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was real proud of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, that's my boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he said, my mother said, well, she said, you didn't do so good in high school.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she said, well, you're still very clumsy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You fell down twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that story has been used quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: You went up to Madison, South Dakota, and it looks like you had a pretty good year up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a very good year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We played sixty-six, I think it was ninety-some ballgames, and I was in sixty-six ballgames as a pitcher and an outfielder.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just have your batting record here.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about your pitching that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you remember how you did?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I won fifteen or sixteen ballgames.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know one time I pitched a doubleheader.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Westinghouse, Queens, I won a doubleheader.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how many games I did play.
[SPEAKER_02]: This would be back in... 1920.
[SPEAKER_02]: You pitched a doubleheader?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nine-inning games, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there wasn't no seven-inning jobs then.
[SPEAKER_01]: They all went the distance.
[SPEAKER_01]: The games were a little faster.
[SPEAKER_01]: You could play nine innings, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was short.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you, were you signed as a pitcher or as an outfielder?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was signed as a pitcher, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You started so many home runs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I made an outfielder out of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: How many did you hit?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no record here of your home run output.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's something that we cannot find a record about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that I hit one home run in the South Dakota League, and I know who I hit it off of, because I hit it off of George Fisher, who was playing with Miller.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the only one that I can recall that I hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was a fella by the name of Pete Turgeon, a truck stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he led the league at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pete Turgeon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He lives in Minneapolis.
[SPEAKER_01]: When did you join them?
[SPEAKER_01]: What month, maybe, in 1920?
[SPEAKER_01]: You weren't with them at the start of the season, were you?
[SPEAKER_01]: With Madison?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I started out in the season.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you go to spring training with anybody that year?
[SPEAKER_02]: We trained in St. Louis while we were there with Ralph Horst and then we went up to Madison, South Dakota.
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole Madison team trained?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: We picked up quite a few ball players from St. Louis.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anybody on that team that made it pretty big on that Madison team?
[SPEAKER_01]: On the Madison team?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I guess I was the only one, but there was some pretty good ball players in the league at that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Al Simmons and Jim Bollombe, they were all up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you pitch against them?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: How'd you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Simmons backed me up pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You weren't the only one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he use the name Simonson or his Polish name?
[SPEAKER_01]: No his name was Simonson.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Jim Bottomley was a fine bloke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know him very well?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just by being in that league.
[SPEAKER_02]: He played with Mitchell.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was a class D league?
[SPEAKER_01]: A class B league, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, how about you get over to Minneapolis that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Minneapolis bought me.
[SPEAKER_01]: They scouted you then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your record must have gotten over to Minneapolis that year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they bought me, so I wasn't going to the ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I pitched three ballgames.
[SPEAKER_02]: After I win one, I beat, I think it was Milwaukee or somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot who it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other two, I lost them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I hit 375.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't play the outfield end with Minneapolis at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was the manager at Minneapolis?
[SPEAKER_02]: Joe Pantilla.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Pongo Joe?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pongo Joe, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was he like?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me a little bit about Joe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he was a very eccentric fella.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a little short, stubby fella.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a pretty sound baseball man, I would say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he was very funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember the day that I hit a triple in the first game that I pitched up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got on third base and I later scored, so I ran in to come in on the plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, let me see your fingers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I looked at him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, well, you're not too sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, my fingers are not sore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he said, I thought you hit that triple on your fist.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hit it a long way.
[SPEAKER_02]: It went off the top of the fence, you know, and bounced back.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he was quite a man.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was he a pretty tough manager or easy going?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had sort of an easy, well, I would say he was a little bit too lenient with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let them do what they wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had no rules on the program.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he had a long career, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: He must have been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was with Washington, I think, for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he was with Washington in the early part of the century.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think he also was a man.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was an umpire.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a little fella.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wasn't very big.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where did this Pongo come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where that name came from, but that's what they call him, Pongo Joe.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a brother, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he own the club?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't seem to deal too much with the ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never saw him around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I was only with the ball club for about three weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that just the end of the season in 20?
[SPEAKER_01]: Finish the season in 20, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, how did you get over here to Tulsa?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tulsa?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's see, how did I get to Tulsa?
[SPEAKER_02]: They optioned me out on option.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're still a Minneapolis property?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still a Minneapolis property, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then, I didn't do too well as a pitcher over in Washington.
[SPEAKER_02]: They hit me pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I kept going out to ballpark and working out, you know, learning to hit and play the outfield.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who was the manager at Tulsa?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bill Clymer.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's C-L-Y-M-E-R?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know much about him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Derby Day Bill, they called him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where'd that come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where he got that name from.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, did he start you when the season began as a regular starting pitcher?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I was relieving all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how many games I didn't hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't hit so well either that year.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I was a lousy pitch hitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some fellas can do that, and I don't know, I couldn't do it too well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Coming off the bench and being all ready to go is pretty hard to do, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says here St. Joseph, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that a...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if... St. Joe in Western Maine?
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody wrote, Bob Davis maybe wrote that in here, that you were in 21 also, you went to St. Joseph?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You traded?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was traded over there to a fella by the name of Dan Tipple.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tipple?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pitcher, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was in 22.
[SPEAKER_02]: In 23, I went to Omaha.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got Des Moines here in 22.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: You got Des Moines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Des Moines, yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: 22.
[SPEAKER_02]: 22, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, how'd you do that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you remember Des Moines?
[SPEAKER_02]: Des Moines?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how many games I won over there, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says 295.
[SPEAKER_01]: You must have played some outfield there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some outfield on first base, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was your manager in Des Moines?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember him?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking of his name.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't think of it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Lee Kaiser, he was the general manager over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then, how about Omaha?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in Omaha, I went over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were being traded around these different clubs here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they were trading around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just a kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could throw hard, but I couldn't get the ball over the floor.
[SPEAKER_01]: You weren't Minneapolis Procter anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they traded me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, in that Dan Tipple deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: You belong just to these clubs you were with then, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Western League.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in 23, I was with the Omaha Club.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we had a fellow by the name of Art Greaves.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a First Nation from the Coast League.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I done very well over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in 1924, I was still with the Omaha Club.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ed Kanetchi, you remember him?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know the name.
[SPEAKER_01]: First baseman was he?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, first baseman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just know the name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well he was managing the ball club and I played for him at first base.
[SPEAKER_02]: At Omaha?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was the Omaha manager?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Griggs was there in 24 or 23 and Kanetchi in 24.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did very well that year at Omaha.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually going to play as a regular.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: outfielder first base 40 home runs yeah 155 runs better than huh is that 155 runs better than for that year for Omaha yeah 24 139 I got here this one says 155 that's a lot of runs that's a lot of runs in it tell me about that year some of your
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know what it was, but I hit a long ball, but I didn't actually like a lot of the other fellas I stacked up quite a bit, going for the long ball all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: As I went on, I'd get kids to come out to the park, you know, and I'd give them 50 cents to pitch batting practice to me where I could learn to hit the ball pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I developed them where they said I couldn't hit the high fastball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I got everybody to pitch batting practice to pitch me high fastball, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I got so I hit that high fastball off the right field with power.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had power, I mean, I could hit a ball all day.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really worked at it then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to work hard to get to where I got to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did Omaha have a park suited for right-hand sluggers?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a big park there, a great big high-signed brick fence in left field.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it must have been 50 or 60 foot high.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you had to hit the ball over that for a whole month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of your home runs go over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hit the ball to right center quite a bit too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it as far out there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could hit a ball pretty good ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that best I would tell you was 375.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on that small club, Omaha Club, they had Dave Herman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heim Manoush, Jimmy Wilcox, a fine ball player.
[SPEAKER_02]: He could have went to the big league but he passed away.
[SPEAKER_02]: George Grantham played second base.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were all good ball players.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was on your team?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they were good balls.
[SPEAKER_01]: You must have won the title of that team.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were good balls.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was Babe Herman like?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: How about Babe Herman?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was he as crazy as they say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was sort of an eccentric sort of a fellow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you what he did one day when I was with the bookman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll get a little bit ahead of the story, but I won't tell you this anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: George's sister was finishing up the season with the Boston Braves, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, his sister was left-handed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's because she had the glove on her right hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had a bad finger.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he had this finger that was knocked off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he had it taped up and he wanted to cut a hole in his glove, you know, so he could put his hand in it and this finger would be on the outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: While Babe Herman was playing first base, he looked over and seen that glove.
[SPEAKER_02]: He goes in and gets the scissors and a knife and cuts two fingers out of his glove, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So finally somebody come up and hit a shot at him, a line drive, and Babe went like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Glove and all, right field.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Wilbur Robinson was a man of the ball club, and he said, maybe, he said, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he said, it's just a guy's glove clicks like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was quite a thot.
[SPEAKER_02]: He could hit though, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, he could.
[SPEAKER_02]: Left-handed too, that didn't make any difference.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, now,
[SPEAKER_01]: How about Heinie Minouche?
[SPEAKER_01]: What kind of a guy was he?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice fellow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw him quite a few times.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that, after that 24th season, we'll get back to that, I was sold to the Yankees.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did they, uh, who scouted you for the Yankees?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bob Connery.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's dead now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Connery.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bob Connery, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that, uh... And did you, uh,
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you have anything to do with any of them that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: With Yankee?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I went spring training with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: 25?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I hadn't planned on it too much and they wanted me to play center field.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Miller Hubbard was the manager of Yankee and said that Bert Niehoff was the manager of Atlanta and said that he wanted me to play center field.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they sent me to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was 1925.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went down there and I had a pretty good year.
[SPEAKER_02]: 28 bases, drove 139 runs, did 30 home runs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Led the leg in homers, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that in Sulfordale?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sulfordale, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tell me about that ballpark there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you remember Sulfordale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was a good ballpark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess it was, well, it was the best ballpark in the Southern Mead, I would say, at that time, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was very well maintained, and the maintenance was kept up fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: How big was the seating capacity?
[SPEAKER_02]: About, I would say, 10, 12,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get most of your home runs there or on the road?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit a lot of them on the road.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it a good home run park, would you say?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a big park.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I hit that ball in between them, it was... No, I mean, that's the reason I hit.
[SPEAKER_01]: On the inside of the park?
[SPEAKER_01]: I could run pretty good on the inside of the park.
[SPEAKER_01]: For a big man, you must have been pretty fast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty fast for a big man.
[SPEAKER_01]: I could run pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, for a big ball, I could.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say, no, it was a ton of bases.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who was, or Nehoff was the manager there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did the Atlanta Club do in 25?
[SPEAKER_01]: We won the pennant.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dixie Series?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dixie Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who else was on the Atlanta team, do you remember any of them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan Mikewell was the owner of the ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: I meant the players on the team.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we had Red Smith.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was third baseman, Rod Murphy was first baseman, Wolver Good played right field, and I played center, Frankie Zowers played left field, Donny Brock was the catcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was the left fielder, Zowers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Frankie Zowers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zowers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, Yerusha was down there as a shortstop for a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did the Yankees have a couple, he was the Yankee proctor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well I was the Yankee proctor.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a working agreement with us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any pictures of Fane?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, there wasn't any pictures of him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you spend training that year at 25 with the Yankees and then a season began and they sent you to Atlanta?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I went to spring training with the Yankees down in St. Petersburg.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, coming back, they wanted me to play the regular, so they dropped me off and
[SPEAKER_02]: It was as if he was between two people, two ballplayers, who he was going to keep for the extra outfielder with the Yankees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ben Paschal, remember him?
[SPEAKER_02]: And me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Paschal had played at Atlanta a year before I got there, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: So they kept him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was older than I was and had more experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they kept him and sent me out.
[SPEAKER_01]: When was it decided you were an outfielder, not a pitcher?
[SPEAKER_02]: While we were in Springtrenum, down there was the Yankees, and Miller Huggins was the manager of the ball club, and he said to me, he said, Nick, he said, I think you can go farther as an outfielder than you would as a pitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I said, well, you're the boss, whatever you want me to do, I'll go ahead and try and do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, okay, so I'm going to make an outfielder out of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's Miller Huggins?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about the Bay that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Any Babe Ruth stories?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: That haven't been told?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I'd say he was more fun than anybody I know of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he call you Kid?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody was named Kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny thing about it, when he was out of baseball, we were playing over in Indianapolis.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he was working, I think, for the Ford Motor Company, or somebody, the goodwill ambassador.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I didn't think that he'd remember me, you know, and I didn't say anything to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, hey, kid, come here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he was sitting right behind the whole plate, him and Donnie Bush.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Donnie Bush?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he owned In-N-Out, I suppose, at that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went up there and he shook hands with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That tickled me.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was after he was through with me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was through with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a goodwill ambassador for some big concern, I don't know which one, but he was sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think Ruth would have ever made a good manager?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: He always felt bitter that he never got a chance to meet him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never saw him as tough baseball with the kids, you know, he was fooling around with them all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he tried to help young kids, you know, to play, and somebody said, hit the ball like he could.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I said, babe, who can hit the ball like you?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he was a fine outfielder and had a good arm and a good pitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: He used to go out there and pitch back practice with us kids.
[SPEAKER_01]: He really couldn't take care of himself well enough to take care of our team that he was managing himself with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they say that he done a lot of things, but I couldn't say anything about what he did or what he didn't do because... Well, it came out in the book, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's in the book.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then you were up... How about 26 now?
[SPEAKER_02]: At 26, I was with him in the spring training again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I went to bat one time with the Yankees, and I got one hit, I won for two, so I was sent out of the American League hitting five hundred.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went to St. Paul, and that was triple-A ball then.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went over there and then... Had a working agreement with the Yankees.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the Yankees, they did, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went, I stayed there one year, and then
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pretty good year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I had a pretty good year over there at St. Paul.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was the manager at St. Paul?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nick Allen.
[SPEAKER_02]: An old catcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rough and tough.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was it at St. Paul, generally?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you like it there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I liked it there very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I spent most of my time up there when we didn't have to work out anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd go fishing up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked to fish quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked it at St. Paul.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was the ballpark?
[SPEAKER_01]: What was the name of the park?
[SPEAKER_01]: Lexington Park.
[SPEAKER_01]: What kind of a park was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a good ballpark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good size.
[SPEAKER_01]: These are all pretty good sized parks, aren't they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You hit a lot of home runs.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really had to earn them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit, I don't know, 24, 25 home runs over there, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how many I did do.
[SPEAKER_02]: 22 I hit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I stole 32 bases.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mostly the big slugger just went too fast in the bases with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then the Yankees must have sold you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They traded me to Washington for Dutch Luther.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Dutch Luther, the left-hand pitcher?
[SPEAKER_02]: They traded me over there to him, and Bucky Harris was manager of Washington.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went over there and I didn't play, well I didn't play any too much at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean I was with Washington and so they decided then they asked waivers on me and the Cleveland club took me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I got over to Cleveland on the waiver.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why didn't you play much with Washington?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had Sam Rice, Bruce Godlin, and Earl McNeely.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why you didn't play.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the reason I didn't play.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a pretty tough outfield to break into.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know when I was with the Yankees, it happened here just a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said, boy, a lot of ballplayers, good minor league ballplayers, went to the big league and didn't play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, he couldn't play there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they said, what kept me from playing every day?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, well, there's four guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: kept me playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to first base with Lou Gehrig, I went to right field here with Ruth, I went to center field here with Earl Combs, and I went to left field here with Bob Musil.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can only play three, so what am I going to play?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't have a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they would have traded me when I was first coming up to the Yankees, I could have played.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that was about the year Combs broke in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gary, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gary, too, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Combs broke in about that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they got the jump play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you like Griffith Stadium?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was a big ballpark.
[SPEAKER_02]: The biggest thrill I got out of that ballpark was seeing Walter Johnson pitch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get to know him very well?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty fine gentleman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine fellow, whoever he was.
[SPEAKER_01]: He probably may have been the greatest pitcher ever, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was so hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: About three quarters from right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: How'd things go over in Cleveland?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play too much over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over in Cleveland, they just took me over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What they was going to do, use me in a deal that next year to speak with managers and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he tell you this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they tell you this?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but you've been around a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use the reading on the wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: The funny thing happened to me, we had a man right here in the conference room, a Jack McAllister who was a scout, a fine little baseball man.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he was the coach over there then, Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he'd use everybody, he had to pitch, hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he was going to send some pitcher up to hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So his speaker forgot about me, so Jack said, no, put that big guy up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he sent me in to pitch, hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was on the run.
[SPEAKER_02]: So as I round the bases, come running around the base, I looked on the bench and there wasn't a soul on the bench.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they'd all give me the silent treatment, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said, don't say nothing to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just walked down, got a drink of water and I said, well, I must be on the wrong bench.
[SPEAKER_02]: I go back over there and they really give it to me then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they just kid you, you mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they were kidding me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where did they go when they weren't on the bench?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did they go?
[SPEAKER_02]: In the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jack McAllister told me to do it, he told that story a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they came back out though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, they mobbed me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where did you hit it?
[SPEAKER_01]: The bleachers or over the fence?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, over the right center field fence I hit it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I grew up in Cleveland so I loved Lake Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had that big high screen up there, but I hit it quite over that screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Opposite field.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I loved that little ballpark.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I did too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you ever have a chance to hit him in the bleachers or weren't you around long enough or play enough to do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't give him a chance to play too much up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a long blow out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, left field was a long blow.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was Speaker?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good baseball man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though he forgot about you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was a good baseball man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Went outfield, could run, throw, and no doubt about it, hit him.
[SPEAKER_01]: How can you manage from center field?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know whether an outfielder, well, there has been outfielders maybe not playing managers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's the only one that was playing manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bucky Harris played second base and he was playing manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd think he'd be a pretty fiery move.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're watching the picture, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he had, they had signs, I mean, when, you know, I just want to walk a man and put him on or things like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember George Yulee?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I interviewed George Yulee last year up in Cleveland.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he told me about, before Speaker was manager, Lee Fole was the manager there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Speaker was kind of Fole's playing manager on the field.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Speaker gave Fole a lot of suggestions and so on from the outfield there, even changing pitchers, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'd forgotten who it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody, Speaker made a signal for Fole to remove the pitcher and put somebody else in.
[SPEAKER_01]: And whoever else went in,
[SPEAKER_01]: was badly hit, and they fired Fole that night.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Speaker felt kind of bad because it was his decision, but I guess Fole was on the way out.
[SPEAKER_01]: George Uley indicated he did have a lot to say before he was manager about how the game was going from center field.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had a good curveball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a great pitcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a good hitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's more proud of his hitting than his pitching, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a little fella in that ball club that I admired pretty well, Charlie Jameson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Charlie Jameson?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a good ball player.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gardner was a good ball player too, third baseman.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a name of a player on that team, I think he was there then, it's always intrigued me, Lutzky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rube Lutzky.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Lutzky?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and he was like a shovel, biggest hands I ever saw anybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rube Lutzky, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't see any good?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was a good ball player.
[SPEAKER_02]: He played for the base most of the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: His hands, he could grab anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he'd throw that ball at first base, mud, dirt, anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: He knew where it was going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How'd he get the Rube?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how he got that name.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a German.
[SPEAKER_02]: He lived in Milwaukee.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was Homer Summa on that team?
[SPEAKER_01]: He'd come later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Biz was up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They called him Biz all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Homer Summa was there, Garland Buckeye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Garland Buckeye, that's a name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was there with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had a picture of him, and Mueller was up there with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: He lives in Cleveland now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to interview him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't had a chance to see him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went up to his house, and he wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_01]: A great big dog was there, so I went away.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'll go back.
[SPEAKER_01]: Luke Sewell, did you know Luke?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was a stretcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: He and Gwen Miles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luke, I played short.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Joe Sewell.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've talked to Luke Sewell, but I haven't had a chance to meet Joe Sewell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, and who sent you to Buffalo?
[SPEAKER_01]: How'd you get to Buffalo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I went over there, Bill Clymer would imagine that ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he and I, I don't know, he didn't like me for some reason, and I cared less for him, if I have to say it myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I finally got over to Buffalo, and then they turned around and sent me, I told them I would get me off the ball club.
[SPEAKER_01]: Were you Cleveland property?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I said, I want to get off the ball club, but I'm not going to play, I don't want to be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they sent me back down to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was 1929, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you like it back in Atlanta or how are you feeling about not staying up in the big time by this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't sit on a bench and I wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I had to sit on a bench, I might just as well be playing in a minor league someplace.
[SPEAKER_01]: As long as you were playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as I was playing, I wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really loved the game, did you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, how about Brooklyn in 1929?
[SPEAKER_01]: They get in the picture here.
[SPEAKER_01]: They drafted me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brooklyn did.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, who was managing Atlanta before we got to Brooklyn?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who was there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wilbur Goode.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was managing Atlanta then.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a fellow of the outfielder the last time you were down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wilbur Goode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wilbur Robinson was managing the Brooklyn ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus Dave Herman played with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We wound up with three men on third base.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was sitting around over there and I wasn't playing, so I asked Robbie, I said, Robbie, there isn't any place for me on this ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, why don't you get rid of me and do something with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he said, where do you want to go?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, I don't care, I'll do something.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they turned around and I went to Minneapolis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in 30.
[SPEAKER_01]: You finished out the season with Brooklyn in 29?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, in 30 I went on to Cincinnati to make a deal for her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mike Kelly bought me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what that deal was.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Mike kept telling me that they owed him another ballplayer for me, see, for my purchase.
[SPEAKER_02]: The purchase price.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Mike said he never did get him.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he kept me over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I stayed there that whole year in Minneapolis.
[SPEAKER_01]: He bought you from Brooklyn?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he was supposed to get somebody else too?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was supposed to get somebody else with you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: He bought me and another ball player that they got for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the purchase price?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what it was, what the purchase price.
[SPEAKER_01]: Players didn't get a chunk of the purchase price in those days, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like they want today.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was Robinson as a manager?
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a good manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: All this talk about the old days, him and John McGraw.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a good manager, a very popular man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tell you what, they had a ball player over there, a young fellow over there, a Wally Gilbert.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you remember him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a great football player.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he was having, got off to a terrific start.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Robbie went up and asked him one day, he says, um, Wally, how much money you making?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, nobody told him, he says, okay, he says, go on, I'll get a new contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he gave him a raise right in the middle of the road.
[SPEAKER_02]: This scene was about three weeks old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he gave him, I don't know how much he got, but he got a good raise.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the owner, who was it, the peever or, whoever the owner was, must have had faith in
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Robby, I guess he owned quite a bit of stock.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he was a field manager, general manager too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he, he knew his baseball all right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he knew the players real well and what they could do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he handled men very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he get tough with them or tough when he had to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he'd get tough, good and tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: When he said it's put down, that was it, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, now you're up at Minneapolis.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is probably your greatest year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tell me about that year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we went to spring training and Al Simmons was holding out with the athletics at that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We trained in the hot springs, Arkansas.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he worked out with us, Simmons did, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, I don't know, he took a liking to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: He helped me do other things about changing my style of hitting on the plate, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was stood, always stood, way in the back of the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: I stepped into the pitch, and they got the ball in tight on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where they pitched, but they couldn't get that ball in all the time, see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: We went on a spring training.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a good spring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit very well with Minneapolis club the next pitch he gave me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we came back up here and we opened up in Toledo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Casey Stengel was manager of the Toledo club.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the first day after Ernie Wingarden was pitching, I guess you remember him, the old pitcher with the St. Louis Browns, first baseman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he was pitching and I had a home run a trip off him.
[SPEAKER_02]: We won a bowl game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The next day,
[SPEAKER_02]: Alec Ferguson was pitching, he hit me in the head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right there I got it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right by the left ear, above the left ear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I was in the hospital for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't have your batting helmet on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't have none, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at that time, every time I'd look at something, I could see it till we got so far that it all turned black.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we came back here to Columbus to play there, and I was out to O'Neill Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I struck out nine straight times.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I could see the ball, you know, as it got right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wasn't that bad of a hitter, if I have to say it myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I struck out nine times in a row.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Mike Kelly said to me, he said, uh, Nick, he said, uh, can you see that ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, I can see it so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, well, why don't you tell me?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, I'll take you out.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, you might get hurt again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he took me out and we went back home then, went back to Minneapolis and we played Toledo again and Rosie Ryan was pitching.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Rosie threw a lot of curveballs and I was guessing with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, well, it's a long curveball, that's a sink.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he threw one up there and I hit it out of the park.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's hittin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played from then on the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, your vision straightened out then, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it did, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Were you knocked out completely?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was knocked cold and, see, because I let him know where I was at, what town I was in or anything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: How long were you out?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you remember Johnny LeVan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Doc LeVan, shortstop, used to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Brown.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a health commissioner there in Toledo.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, you better get him to the hospital, so they took him down to the hospital.
[SPEAKER_02]: I stayed, I guess I was out, oh, maybe a couple of hours, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the guy that hit me, he never came down to see me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Wingard, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alec Ferguson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that was one of...
[SPEAKER_01]: He was probably afraid to, maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe he was afraid to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if I could see him.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I got back and started to play, and I done all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you certainly did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kelly, was he the manager or the owner, or both?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was the manager and the owner.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who else was on that team?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we had... Was Joe Hauser on that team?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he came after us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had Wes Griffin, Eddie Sicking.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've interviewed him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Frank Hemmer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eddie Sicking.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's down in Cincinnati.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that so?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leo Cotter.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had him over there in Spencer-Harris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew Benton, remember him?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody knows him.
[SPEAKER_02]: The old left-hand pitcher with Cincinnati.
[SPEAKER_01]: So then... Well, where'd you hit most of those home runs?
[SPEAKER_01]: Home run or everywhere, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hit them everywhere, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was... What was the name of that park?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nicklin Park.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was Nicklin Park.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What were the dimensions there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, left field was about 350 and right field was only about 250.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I didn't hit too many balls over that right field fence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Down the center field was 400.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this park was built for a left hand hitter like Buzz Orlette, Howser and those fellows.
[SPEAKER_02]: They stand there and hit balls on their fists.
[SPEAKER_01]: There really wasn't any park built for right-hand hitters, were there?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the American Association?
[SPEAKER_02]: There wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a funny thing about the baseball house, the right-field fence is always shorter than the left-field fence.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the left-hand hitter, he's got the advantage of going first base.
[SPEAKER_01]: More sluggers were left-handers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Was it more sluggers were left-handers or more short right-field walls made left-hand hitters the sluggers?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which it is there, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did the team do that year overall?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you win?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we finished way down, I don't know, fourth or fifth place, something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everywhere in 1930, the home runs were flying out of all the ballparks and the majors and minors.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did they do that year?
[SPEAKER_01]: The ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know whether the ball was lively or whether they changed the ball or what it was, but I saw some ball get through that entry like bullets.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, he was a braver, he assaulted the fuller ball real good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know when I come up to Hickory, they played the third baseman.
[SPEAKER_02]: He played the butters quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he played so deep, you know, they couldn't throw me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Mike Kelly said, Nick, he started watching the butler more.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, people come out here to see you, we don't want none.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ruth used to bark quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he'd get up and play him way back and he'd dump that ball and run down to first base and land.
[SPEAKER_01]: Players can't bunt today.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the best bunter I've seen so far is this kid pitcher they got over there at Cincinnati.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gullet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gullet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's a very good bunter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a good hitter too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: He can play outfield when his pitching days are over.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was it like up in Swain Park or Swainfield?
[SPEAKER_02]: Swainfield was a big ballpark, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It never kept up to where I am now.
[SPEAKER_01]: How were these American Association dressing room facilities?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, we're talking about these facilities in these, you know, locker rooms and things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, out here in the Redbird Stadium, they had a real nice big roomy clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody had boxes of their own.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kansas City was in the league.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a good clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: So did Louisville.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was Muehlebach Field there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Muehlebach Field?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Muehlebach Field, yeah, Muehlebach.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Minneapolis Division clubhouse up there, you had a dressing room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Half the team one time, they'd get dressed and you'd be back in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a very small clubhouse they had in Indiana.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they had shower facilities?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: In all these places?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you ever play any place where you had to dress in the hotel and go to the ballpark?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bus or cab or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exhibition games is all.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about travel?
[SPEAKER_01]: How did you travel?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I would travel.
[SPEAKER_02]: At that time, we traveled by train.
[SPEAKER_02]: What were those train trips like?
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we used to go on the Western League.
[SPEAKER_02]: We used to travel in those old cars, old tourist cars, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was so hot you couldn't sleep anyway, and we'd open up the windows and send them to come in on top of you all night long.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't have Pullman's?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Pullman cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then, after we got back,
[SPEAKER_02]: years after that where they started to fly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, sometimes we made a lot of trips, like from here to Indianapolis, we rode on a bus.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you stayed in the best hotels?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we stayed in good hotels.
[SPEAKER_01]: How much money did they give you on the trips, expense money?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two dollars a day.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that enough?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's what they got.
[SPEAKER_02]: They got two dollars a day and then they finally raised it to two and a half.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then I went to Big Big, they got five dollars a day.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did they, did they give you two dollars each day or did they give you money before that trip?
[SPEAKER_02]: I say if you went into a town to play for three days, they give you six dollars.
[SPEAKER_01]: The traveling secretary with you all the time handed out the money, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he make room assignments in hotels or did he just room with anybody he wanted?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he'd room with whoever he wanted to.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'd go right in, he'd take their bags in if he wanted to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they have bed checks?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did anybody ever get caught out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of them did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure did.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd they do to them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: What would they do to them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything just fine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, they'd probably fine them $10-15 and after any season they'd give it back to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you ever caught out?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Were there any comedians or jokesters or high livers on any of your teams?
[SPEAKER_01]: were always in trouble or out, you know, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the only fellow that we had that I knew that was in trouble all the time by me was Art Shiler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Art the Great?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he played there.
[SPEAKER_02]: He got in trouble quite a few times.
[SPEAKER_02]: He and Timmy Adel were really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But besides the rest of the ballplayers and managers, I always played first.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'd say, if you want to
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, go ahead and drink one after the ball game.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, but don't try to stir that dick at all one night, which was very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the ball clubs, the managers, you know, if you have a good tough series, like your doubleheader on a Saturday, good and hot, they buy you beer in the clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did a lot of the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, a couple of cases, which would only be a bottle apiece, and they carried 24 in both places.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a manager, do you have any trouble with players?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I never have.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only trouble I ever had, I had a ball player that, he's always late.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's never on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I let him get away with it the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I said, now look, this is the first time I'm warning you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, next time you come out late, you can stay wherever you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't come to the ballpark, because you're not doing me any good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three days later, we'd already had a meeting.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a meeting in the clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you with Columbus now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm with Columbus now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, this fella's name was Charlie Grumbolo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, he had some trouble with his wife, and his wife came out to the parking, he had a ring where he had hit her and left an imprint on her face.
[SPEAKER_01]: He hit her?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he hit his wife, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he came out to Parkway and I wouldn't let him in the club.
[SPEAKER_02]: We was having our reading period.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the clubhouse boy said Bumble was outside, I said let him stay outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I fined him $25, which was all pretty lenient.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, of course, I didn't want to make him too much money.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I fined him $25 and suspended him three days.
[SPEAKER_02]: From then on then he's the first guy at the ballpark, but I give his money back after the season.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty hard to make that a lot, to have somebody who don't take it away from you.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't cheat, but he didn't mean either.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't get drunk all the time, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'd get drunk when he wanted to hit his wife.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you probably, as a manager, the best way was to be reasonable with them, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fair, but have certain rules and regulations.
[SPEAKER_01]: They love to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there must have been some big league teams after you after that 30 season.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's quite true.
[SPEAKER_01]: What happened then?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he sold me to Cincinnati.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kelly did.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went to Cincinnati before the season was over in Manhattan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to Cincinnati, I think I played in seven ballgames after the season was over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't hit too well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't hold an 82.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the seven games with Dan Holley was managing the ball club.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the next year, uh, I stayed with Cincinnati all year and I hit 260.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was Holly still manager?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what'd you, what'd you play center field?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, right field.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who were the other players on that, uh, 31 team?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had Joe Stiff, Harvey Hendricks, Tony Cucinella, Leo DeRocher, Red Lucas, Eppa Rixey, and, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: Clyde Stookes, fourth, from the Chessers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marvin Hendricks played first base.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huey Critts, was he with you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huey Critts, or Critts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Second baseman.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Crutzenella.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stookes played third.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had a pretty good infield in the Ocean in the shortstop.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we didn't have no picks for Red Lucas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Richie was the best pick we had.
[SPEAKER_01]: Richie's pretty much over the hill, then, wasn't he?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Larry Benton would go over that hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a pretty good pitcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, uh, what happened after 31?
[SPEAKER_01]: 31?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they release you, or trade you, or sell you?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Cardinals bought me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I knew then, when the Cardinals bought me, I'd never seen the ballpark in St. Louis.
[SPEAKER_02]: How'd you know that?
[SPEAKER_02]: They put me on auction for their farm club, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they bought me, and I never even put on a Cardinal uniform.
[SPEAKER_02]: They bought me and auctioned me out to Columbus.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did you know that you wouldn't
[SPEAKER_01]: play in St. Louis?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because of the outfield they had?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because of the outfield they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were world champions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would they get you to option you out?
[SPEAKER_02]: They bought me from Cincinnati.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: If they had an outfield that was pretty well set, I wonder why they would...
[SPEAKER_01]: They needed outfielders in the farm system.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you went to Rock?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you train with the Cardinals at all?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I came to Columbus then.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had a pretty good year in Billy Sopper as the manager of the ball club.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the year they opened the new park, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: In 32, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was Leroy Parmalee on that team?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who?
[SPEAKER_01]: Parmalee?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've talked to him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he remembers that first year when we had the ball park.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I got the first base here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We never got to the ballpark out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: River City, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We never got to the ballpark.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no ballpark out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beautiful park.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen a lot of games there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just a shame it's run down now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and, um... You ever get a fun feeling?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: You ever drive by there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Get a funny feeling?
[SPEAKER_02]: I get a funny feeling, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went back there and walked back in and looked at home plate and his horse with his eyes just...
[SPEAKER_01]: I imagine he would.
[SPEAKER_00]: He dies a thousand times.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the scene of so many great moments in your life and it's just...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a shame that Thomas doesn't take care of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a shame they never supported the teams here in the later years.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did they support baseball when you were with them?
[SPEAKER_01]: We drew $325,000 one year, which is very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think we had gone too bad while the Cardinals were here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, of course, the Cardinals, they were in here from 1932 to 1936.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's when I was trained.
[SPEAKER_02]: About 20 years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right into the 50s I think they owned them.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Jets came in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who were some other players in that 32 Redbird team?
[SPEAKER_01]: 32?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we had Kenny Ashe, the one who was a pitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bud Parnley, Kenny O'Day,
[SPEAKER_02]: Francis Healy, another catcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bill Lee was with him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bill Lee, Connor Lee, Al Guboski, a left-hand pitcher.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about the outfield beside you?
[SPEAKER_01]: They had me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tell me a little bit about Bevo Labarrua, I'm always fascinated by that name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bevo was a good hitter, left hand hitter, hit a ball hard, pull the ball, run, pretty good outfielder, pretty good ball player.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty nice chap?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, he was alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why you call him Bevo?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why he ever got that name of Bevo.
[SPEAKER_01]: His name was DeWitt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I know DeWitt.
[SPEAKER_01]: We wouldn't probably call him DeWitt.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'd be giving that name to Bebo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bebo the Barber.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a 33 club when we really had a good ball club.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you had a pretty good year then, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: 43 runs back then.
[SPEAKER_01]: 22 triples.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: How'd you get so many triples?
[SPEAKER_01]: To me that's the sign of an all-around ballplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of triples because you have to hit the ball hard, you have to be able to run, slide probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's the most exciting hit in the ballgame, the triple, where the fella has to run around and has to hit the third base.
[SPEAKER_01]: That to me is one of Clemente, remember Roberto Clemente?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Pirates, one of his attributes of greatness because he led the, he was the far ahead of all other active players at triples when he was killed.
[SPEAKER_01]: He could not only hit high for high average and field well, but he had a lot of triples.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit three triples in one game on them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hit them right in between, this was a big field where you,
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you ever run through a stop signal at second?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not seeing it or just thinking you could get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't run with my head down.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't see it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't see the coach give me a stop sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you run with your head down you can't see it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They tell you when you get back to the bench.
[SPEAKER_01]: They fine you for that?
[SPEAKER_01]: They'd shoot me up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a pretty good question for him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, well, I thought I could make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, hell, I got a better chance on third base than I had on second to score.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, where are you going to score from now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, I'm going back to Vince.
[SPEAKER_01]: Were you out at any times you ran through the stop sign?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he ever get you out at third?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he got me out.